### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Tiwit Technology Solutions Pvt Ltd
Senior Visual Designer, Bangalore, India | 2022 - 2023

A digital healthcare service aggregator startup.

Joined as a Senior Visual Designer. Guided and managed the design team by training junior designers, collaborated with the content team to create social media campaigns, offline event and business development deliverables. Directed and quided in video productions.

#### Vedantu Innovations Pvt. Ltd.

Creative Graphic Designer, Bangalore, India | 2021 - 2022

An e-learning platform/ educational technology company.

Joined as a creative graphic designer. Designed quality online and offline overall deliverables for company's big launch at Muzaffarpur, Gujarat. Introduced illustrative designs in company's creatives and explored the possibilities of collaborative designs.

#### **TID Communication**

Creative Visualizer, Kochi, India | 2021

The digital wing of Turrino, a prominent advertising agency in Kochi.

Joined as a creative visualiser and later set to explore the field of designing further. Guided the team to create exceptional social media campaigns, videos and other deliverables related to branding and advertising of multiple brands.

#### Collabu Technologies

Graphic designer & Illustrator, Bangalore, India | 2019-2021

An application development start-up.

Joined as a graphic designer, managed overall in-house creative designs for both offline and online platforms. Gained experience in UI/UX designs and other design deliverables including banners, presentation designs and social media creatives.

#### Causate Branding Pvt Ltd

Junior Graphic Designer, Bangalore, India | 2018 - 2019

An advertising agency with years of experience in both offline and online advertising, video production and branding.

Gained experience in designing for branding works, social media campaigns, request for proposals and other business development deliverables. Also worked as an Ad Film Art Assistant



# JIBIN KRISHNA

Creative Visualiser & Illustrator

## **ABOUT ME**

I am an Illustrator and graphic designer with innovative ideas and a distinctive visual style. I have over five years of experience developing designs for the web, print, film, illustrations, layout, and branding. My strength lies in strong attention to detail and the ability to create appealing designs. I like being part of a creative and passionate team. I love to learn new things, and be creative in every aspects of my life:)

# **CONTACT**

Kaniparambil (H) Kachinikkad Makkaraparamba P.O Malappuram Dist Kerala-676507

jibinkrishnan91@gmail.com

+91 9037 161 291

# Freelance Artist and Designer 2012 - 2018

During the course of studies in college, gained experience as an art instructor, art assistant in ad films, theatres and other productions including commercial works as a freelance artist and designer.

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of fine arts | 2014-2018

Govt. College of Fine Arts, Thrissur-Kerala

#### KGCE in fine arts | 2012-2014

National school of fine arts, Manjeri-Kerala

#### SSLC & HSC | 2010-2012

Govt. Vocational Higher Secondary School Makkaraparamba-Kerala

# **SOFTWARE SKILLS**









# **INDUSTRY**

Health & Wellness | Fashion & Lifestyle | Ed-Tech E-commerce | Advertising & Media | Sports-Tech Social Media | Print Media | Retail

# **AREAS OF EXPERTISE**

Digital designing | Typography designing Branding | Art direction | Illustrations | Drawing Sketching | Teaching of art & design | Film making Script writing | Sculpting

# **LANGUAGE**

English, Malayalam Tamil, Hindi (Beginner)

